On February 22 of this year, the Verkhovna Rada of
22 февраля чего года Верховная Рада
Ukraine appointed a non-regular
Украины назначила в не очередные выборы
presidential election until May 25, this is stated in the
президента до 25 мая об этом говорится в
text of resolution number 41, read
тексте постановления номер 41 прочита
the resolution, the text of the resolution,
постановление текст постановления
taking into account that the President of Ukraine Viktor
учитывая что президент Украины Виктор
Yanukovych self-removed
Янукович самоустранение
constitutional
конституционных
powers Good evening Hello, I am
полномочий Добрый вечер Здравствуйте я
from Ukraine, the city of Khmelnitsky, you are
из Украины город Хмельницкий вы
Khmelnitsky, I am from Moscow  areas of ours
Хмельницкий Я из Московской области ших
I know the special operation, support it, yes
знаю тако спецоперацию поддержите да
Super Do you have any questions for me? How do you
Супер Ко мне вопросы есть какие-то чем
communicate about
общаетесь о
the special operation?  what do you think I think that those
спецоперации что думаете думаю что те
who support
кто поддерживает
the special operation Why do I have such an
спецоперацию Почему у меня есть такое
opinion because an adequate person
мнение потому что адекватный человек не
cannot support the special
может поддерживать спецо
operation wait for the special operation is not
чуне Подождите спецоперации не является
people in a foreign country the purpose of the special operation
людей в чужой стране подо целью
is to stop
спецоперации является
their people in a foreign country
остановка своих людей в чужой стране
the purpose of the special operation is to stop you understand
цель спецоперации остановить понимаете
this during E in  time of a special operation of
это во врем Е во время спецоперации
people une that during a special operation of
людей уне что во время спецоперации
people in Ukraine time dest it is
людей в Украине времяни дест это
inevitable people yes that means
неизбежно людей да то есть вот значит
a special operation cannot take place without
спецоперация не может происходить без
people the truth cannot yes that is means
людей правда не может да то есть значит
you  you support people, that means it’s
вы поддерживаете людей значи это ж
clear, we proved everything, no. If before
Понятно Всё мы доказали нет Если до
the special operation you looked at three people three
спецоперации вы людей е три сри е
times, you didn’t understand the year they attacked
раз смотрите Вы ВМ году напали на
Ukraine,
Украину
you are,
не понимаете вы есть Угу разве это
Yeah, is that clear? It’s just that we just agreed on everything. Well, look, that is, you are in the
договорили Ну да смотрите То есть вы в
fourteenth year  people in Ukraine came and began to
четырнадцатом году пришли начали людей в
seize our territories.
Украине захватывать наши территории Вот
And now you continue to do so now, well, in the
и сейчас продолжаете вать теперь ну в
fourteenth
четырнадцатом
year after the military coup Ukraine And
году после военного переворота Украина А
where was the military coup in Ukraine
где был военный переворот в Украине
Ukraine what wait don’t let us
Украина какой подождите не давайте
and what didn’t happen Which military took power
а что не было Какие военные взяли власть
from us military coup
у нас военный переворот жённый
illegal illegal coup Wait what did you say military coup let’s do it like that military transfer wait don’t you
военный вяли перево подожди не вы
let’s understand everything So we caught the
давайте так всё понял Значит поймали
first military armed where we had an
первое военный вооружённый где у нас был
armed coup and  Well, tell me,
вооружённый переворот а Ну скажите что
where did we overthrow someone
где у нас кого у нас перевернули
armed? How did you
вооружённого Как у вас на каком
overthrow Yanukovych? It’s not
основании свергли Януковича у нас не
Swer Yanukovych.  you were overthrown No, don’t
Свер Януковича у вас свергли Нет не
overthrow Yanukovych Are you on what
свергать Януковича Вы что на каком
basis Yanukovych What document did
основании Янукович Каким документом у
we overthrow Yanukovych On what basis
нас свергли Януковича На каком основании
was Yanukovych removed from power we were
был Янукович отстранён от власти нас он
not removed Where are you Show me
не был отстранён Где вы Покажите мне
the document on the removal of Yanukovych now
документ об отстранении Януковича сейчас
Yanukovych is president no
Янукович является президентом нет
wait we still have elections  passed with us
подождите ещё у нас выборы прошли у нас
after it was Poroshenko Yanukovych
уже после него был Порошенко Янукович
is the president of Ukraine if he
является президентом Украины если он не
was not removed on the grounds of e see you
был отстранён на основани е смотрите Вы
they said that they were removed from some
сказали что от отстраняются каким-то
document, it’s true that you overthrew Yanukovych, don’t
документом правда вы свергли Янукович не
look, grandpa, let’s do this if you
смотри дедушка давайте так если вы
said that we removed you, you can say by
сказали что мы отстранили можете сказать
what document Yanukovych was removed
Каким документом был отстранён Янукович
Well, you should know
Ну вы должны знать
that Yanukovych was
вым Янукович был
from that is, Yanukovych at the time of the election of
от то есть Янукович на момент выбора
Poroshenko was the president of Ukraine
Порошенко был президентом Украины
Yes, seriously  yes That is, you think so Well,
Да серьёзно да То есть вы так считаете
he was the president of Ukraine Well, yes, that
Ну он был президентом Украины Ну да то
is, the Verkhovna Rada will not illegally
есть его Верховная Рада незаконно не
remove him So where show me if you
отстранят Так где покажите мне если вы
said that  Verkhovna Rada, you don’t know
сказали что Верховная Рада вы не знаете
what happened in 14,
что у вас происходило в 14 ещё раз
look again at the Verkhovna Rada, did you read
смотрите Верховная Рада вы читали
the resolution of the Supreme Council of the
постановление Верховного Совета
Verkhovna Rada? Well, find me where it
Верховной Рады А ну Найдите мне где
says that it removes Yanukovych, you say
написано что она отстраняет Януковича вы
that I am a person with a legal education,
что я человек с юридическим образованием
wait, wait, let’s look,
подождите подождите давайте давайте
let’s look, you said
давайте будем искать давайте вы сказали
that she
что она
pulled away I’ll find the decree let’s
отстранилась найду постанову давайте
let’s
давайте
you said pulled away Let’s see now we
вы сказали отстранилась Посмотрим сейчас
’ll prove that you’re here or just don’t
докажем что вы тут или просто не
understand, I’m a person with a chess background
разбираетесь вот я человек с ческом обва
let’s let’s
давайте давайте
let’s find no  so I want you to
давайте нашли не так Я ж хочу чтобы вы
read, I know that there is no such resolution
зачитали Я знаю что такое постановление
where she removes
нету где она отстраняет
Yanukovych, on
Януковича вот
February 2 of this year the Verkhovna Rada announced
2 февраля года Верховная Рада объявила
that he is a samora Read This is where you
что он самора Прочитайте Это где вы
read this you are
читаете это вы
somewhere Read the resolution of the
где-то Прочитайте постановление
Verkhovna Rada if there is such a thing and not
Верховной рады если есть такое а не
just that someone-  then he said what the
просто что кто-то сказал что там
Verkhovna Rada
Верховная Рада
did there
сделал
Wait, okay, you need a resolution
Подождите Хорошо вам надо Постановление
on the removal of Yuko Yes, I’m sad that such a
об отстранении Юко Да я горю что такого
resolution was not good, we’ll
постановления не было хорошо будем
look for a
искать
resolution from the Verkhovna Rada on
постановление Верховной Рады от
the removal  Yanukovych from the authorities does not have
отстранения Януковича от власти нету
such a
такого
resolution, you see in your ears your
постановления вам видите вам в уши ваши
propagandists and you repeat, you
пропагандисты и вы повторяете Вы же даже
didn’t even look,
не смотрели
maybe the law is supremely
может так закон верховно
happy about depriving Viktor Yanukovych of the title of
рады о лишении Виктора Януковича звания
president, this title was already in what
президента это звание это уже в каком
year, so now now it’s not the
году было так сейчас сейчас это уже не
same, this title  he was deprived of it, and on
то вот это звание его лишили вот вот вот
February 22, 1914, the Verkhovna
22 февраля четырнадцатого года Верховная
Rada of Ukraine appointed a non-regular
Рада Украины назначила в не очередные
presidential election until May 25, this is
выборы президента до 25 мая об этом
stated in the text of resolution number
говорится в тексте постановления номер
41 full text of the resolution, taking into account
41 повный текст постановления учитывая
that the President of Viktor Yakovi saural from the
что президент у Вик якови саурал от
replenishment of constitutional powers,
пополнения конституционных полномочий
which poses a threat to the governance of
Что представляет угроз для управляемости
the state and the territorial integrity
государством и территориальной цельности
and sovereignty of Ukraine, a massive
и суверенитета Украины массового
violation of the rights and freedoms of citizens, the
нарушения прав и свобод граждан
Verkhovna Rada, expressing the sovereign will of
Верховная Рада выражая суверенную волю
the people, will restore to establish that the
народа восстановят установить что
President of Ukraine Viktor Yanukovych
президент Украины Виктор Янукович не
removed himself in an unconstitutional manner  from
конституционным способом отстранился от
exercising constitutional powers and does not
соления конституционных полномочий и не
fulfill his duties in
выполняет своих обязанностей в
accordance with paragraph this part of Article
соответствии с пунктом сеь часть статьи
85 of the Constitution to appoint  not the next
85 Конституции назначить не очередные
elections so super yes this is this is the
выборы так супер да это вот это есть
resolution This is the first point
постановление Это первый пункт
one How can the President of Ukraine
первый Каким образом президент Украины
self-removal
самоустранение
about removal in an unconstitutional way Yana is not there find the
об отстранение Яну там нету найдите
word removal removes Find the
слово отстранение отстраняет Найдите
word there
такое слово там
this is
это
the Resolution on removal So find the
Постановление об отстранении Так найдите
word find the word remove The Verkhovna
слово найдите слово отстранять Верховная
Rada removes
Рада отстраняет
Yanukovych if  I’m glad to call not the
Януковича если рада назначает не
next election,
очередные выборы
in fact, removal You read,
фактически отстранение Вы прочитали вот
look, you are by training I’m a lawyer I’m a
смотрите Вы кто по образованию Я юрист Я
super lawyer So let’s be like two lawyers
юрист супер Вот давайте как два юриста
You read You  you read the
Вы прочитали Вы прочитали документ
legal document, so a normative legal act
юридический так нормативно-правовой акт
Yes, you claimed that it said something
Да вы утверждали что там что-то сказано
about removal, but you read and did not
про отстранение но прочитали и не
see the word removal, that there is a
увидели слово отстранение что там есть
statement of a legal fact, but no, a
констатация юридического факта так нет
false statement, that’s a hundred, you
ложная констатация это сто это вы
think it’s false, you, as a lawyer, So you
считаете что ложная вы как юрист Так вы
think that  this resolution is not
считаете что это постановление Не
constitutional, so absolutely. Let's do it
конституционно так абсолютно Вот давайте
this way according to the Constitution of Ukraine. Which body
так по Конституции Украины Какой орган
determines the constitutionality or non-
определяет конституционность или не
constitutionality of this or that
конституционность того или иного
normative legal act? Absolutely
нормативного правого акта Абсолютно
true. Look, even I already believe
верно Вот смотрите вы даже я уже верю
that you are a lawyer, probably so.  you also
что вы юрист навер так вот у вас же тоже
have, like, a constitutional court and it is also
есть вроде конституционный суд и тоже он
endowed with such powers, you can
наделён такими полномочиями можете мне
tell me if the constitutional one Well, there was no
сказать если конституционный Ну не было
constitutional filing Yes Is it considered
конституционного подани Да Считается ли
More precisely, is it not so, can I or
Точнее не так могу ли я или
you determine the constitutionality or non-
вы определять конституционность или не
constitutionality of a particular
конституционность того или иного
normative legal act, this must be
нормативно-правового акта это должен
done  constitutional court but you
сделать конституционный суд но вы
replaced wait no no no stop stop stop
заменили подожди нене не стоп стоп стоп
now we are now we are talking about the constitutional
сейчас мы сейчас мы про конституционный
court now we are talking about the constitutional court
суд сейчас мы про конституционный суд
let's go look let's do that means
пойдём смотри давайте так значи значит
you as a Lawyer states that
вы как Юрист констатирует что
there is no decision
никакого решения Конституционного суда
So there was no appeal
поэтому не было обращение было Может там
to the Constitutional Court. Maybe Yanukovych appealed to the Constitutional
Янукович обращался там в Конституционный
Court there. Well, he did. No, that’s exactly what I’m
суд Ну обращался Нет вот именно ва
asking, in general there was no
спрашиваю общ общ не было
constitutional tax, like in Russian, for
конституционного подани както по-русски
example, when you
у вас вот например Когда у вас В
had a constitutional crisis in ninety-three,
девяносто третьем был конституционный
so When Yeltsin dissolved
кризис так Когда Ельцин распустил
parliament  so then there was an appeal to the
парламент так вот тогда было обращение в
Constitutional Court Yes, the constitutional
Конституционный суд Да конституционный
court began to consider and then Yeltsin
суд начал рассматривать и тогда Ельцин
dispersed the constitutional court That
разогнал конституционный суд Вот это
was it Yes, that’s what  you had a
было Да вот вот у вас был
constitutional coup And then look,
конституционный переворот А тут смотрите
no one dispersed the Constitutional Court,
конституционный суд никто не разгонял
so it acted like wait now now now
так он действовал как подождите сейчас
now we will get to this
сейчас сейчас сейчас мы к этому дойдём
wait now now we will get to this
подождите сейчас сейчас мы к этому
wait now we will get to this
подождите сейчас мы к этому дойдём
So you and I have just, as a lawyer, a
Значит мы только что с вами как юрист
lawyer, determined that the Constitutional
юристом определили что Конституционный
Court  I didn’t receive an appeal either from Yanukovych
Суд не получал обращения ни от Януковича
or from the deputies. And the majority of the Party of
не от депутатов А большинство Партии
Regions was and for this resolution
Регионов было да и за это постановление
you can look at the deputy, I can
Вы можете посмотреть депутат я могу
say a standard phrase, all this
стандартную фразу сказать всё это
happened under the lamas of the machine  this is all this is all
происходило под лами автома это это всё
this is all look this is all your opinion
ва это всё смотрите это всё ваше мнение
So you can see Yes voting
Так вы можете посмотреть Да голосование
Which of the deputies specifically voted for
Кто из депутатов конкретно голосовал за
which against Who abstained Who was
кто против Кто воздержался кто
absent so deputies from the Party of
отсутствовал так депутаты из Партии
Regions Yes Yanukovych's associates also
Регионов Да Соратники Януковича тоже
voted For this so what did
голосовали За это так а что сделали с
the Party of Regions do with the office
офисом партия
more  If you're a
регио ещ раз давайте вате
lawyer, you're a lawyer, let
юрист вы юрист давайте
's go No, don't rush, let's not run away
мы Нет не спешите давайте так не убегали
with the party's office, so let's go
с офисом парти значит давайте так мы
underground first, I'll get you wet, I'll get you wet  that
подзем первое я вас мокну мокну вну что
you were deceived, that the resolution was about
вы Обманули что постановление было по
removal, you and I sorted
отстранение мы с вами разобрались
it out, what's leaked, let's look into
слите давайте мы разбираемся с
the resolution
постановлением
with the office of the
сде офисом
couple, what did they do with the office of the regio party?
пар что сделали с офисом партии регио
Because it was burned, burned, spills, if
Потому что его сожгли сожгли разли сли
all this is of no interest to anyone, we
всё это никого не интересует мы
are looking at constitutionality or not
смотрим конституционность или не
constitutionality, other
конституционность Ино
normative Come, everyone  mafia into the
нормативно Приходите все мафии в зал
voting hall and force the
голосований и заставляете
countries to vote as
страм голосовать так как
you do, this is a coup, once again no, you are like a
вы это есть переворот ещ раз нет вы как
lawyer, wait
юрист Подождите ещ
again, according to the decree, you  ran away
раз по постановлению вы убегали потому
because I caught you from the fact that you didn’t know
что я вас поймал из того что вы не знали
caught look caught because you
поймал смотрите поймал потому что вы
said that you were suspended we made out that you were
сказали что отстранили мы разобрали что
n’t suspended ladies the topics are actually not
не отстранили дамы темы те фактически не
actually this is already your nonsense we didn’t have the
фактически это уже ваши бред мы не было
word otst the second you and I determined
слова отст второе мы с вами определили
that there was no appeal from Yanukovych
что никакого обращения Януковича
court look How long Yanukovych is no longer in
суд смотрите Сколько Янукович уже не в
Ukraine already
Украине уже
started playing a
заиграли
long time ago for me the Sun is too early What is the mistake of the Russians
давности мне ВС рано Какая ошибка россий
not the Russian authorities look it means
не российской власти смотри значит
why Yanukovych if he believed that this
почему Янукович если он считал что это
resolution was not constitutional did not
постановление не конституционно не
appeal  They didn’t let me ask a question to the Constitutional
обратился в Конституционный
Court, they
суд вопрос задавать
didn’t give it to me, it’s possible.
не дали не предоставили таю возможно Ну
Well, look who didn’t give it to him. Well,
так Смотрите кто ему кто ему не давал Ну
what Yanukovych himself says about this
что сам Янукович по этому поводу говорит
again, why didn’t he file? Let’s
ещё раз почему он не подал Давайте
ask
спросим
Why didn’t he file an appeal to the
Почему а не подал обращение в
Constitutional Court regarding
Конституционный суд по поводу
removal from power Now  I'll
отстранения от власти Сейчас я его
ask him I'll dial a minute Uh-huh Why lo
спрошу наберу минутку Угу Почему ло
Put me through to Viktor Fedorovich yes yes
Соедините с Виктором фёдоровичем да да
Come on here Kato Russia is asking why
Давай тут Като России спрашивают почему
he is informing the constitutional court
он сообщаю конституционный суд
Yes Fedorovich How's it going  Rostov Yes You
Да Фёдорович Как там в Ростове Да
miss the ostrich Listen here,
Скучаешь да по страусом Слушай тут
in short, someone from Russia asks
короче какой-то из России спрашивает
why you haven’t sent it to the
почему ты не подал до сих пор в
Constitutional
Конституционный
Court yet Yes, he says that one In short,
суд послать Да он говорит что оди Короче
don’t distract
не отвлекайте
him Maybe you can call me Yanukovych
его Может может вы позвоните я Янукович
went to court regarding his removal from
обратился в суд по поводу отстранения от
power when  and for what reason And in
власти когда и по какому поводу И в
what court anu find what Kiev
какой суд ану найдите какой Киевский
answer now you will get an answer what
ответ сейчас вам будет ответ какого
date now now You look at this is not
числа сейчас сейчас Вы посмотрите это не
about that matter let's yeah Let's love
о том дело давайте угу Давайте да люблю
fry lawyer lawyer  it's
прожаривают юрист юриста прожаривается
just a pleasure to be fried, so what kind of
просто наслаждение что ж там Янукович в
court did Yanukovych appeal to? Well, about what?
какой он суд обращался Ну и Насчёт чего
So it turns out that Yanukovych appealed to the
Так оказывается Янукович обращался в
Constitutional Court, which
Конституционный суд какой
constitutional court did he appeal to when
конституционный суд он обращался когда
Ukrainian? However, in the nineteenth year, the
украинский Однако в девятнадцатом году
Constitutional Court of Ukraine refused to
конституционный суд Украины отказал в
consider the claim due to the fact that the
рассмотрении иска из-за того что
conflict was of a political nature  and
конфликт носит политический характер и
therefore it is still in full swing, you can
поэтому находится в ещ разг можете
say where where you think that Yanukovych
сказать где где вы считаете что Янукович
appealed to the Constitutional Court
обратился в Конституционный суд
Let's consider the District Administrative
Давайте счита окружной административный
Court
суд
District  this is not a constitutional court,
Окружной это не конституционный суд
listen, you are pretending to be a
слушайте вы же вы же притворяетесь
lawyer, listen, Well, the district
юристом вот слушайте Ну окружной
administrative court of Kiev has registered a claim by the ex-president of Ukraine Yanukovych about the illegality of his removal from power, this was reported by the representative of the Verkhovna Rada in the constitutional court Olga Sovgirya,
окружном административном суде города
a claim has been registered in the district administrative court of Kiev  former
Киева зарегистрирован иск бывшего
President Yanukovych So she said, that
президента Януковича Вот она сообщила то
is, there was a lawsuit. What kind of court was the lawsuit, but the court
есть иск был Какой суд иск был но суд
refused to
отказался его
consider it? The lawyer
рассматривать юрист мне
is lying to me, the Ukrainians are constantly lying. Here you are
врёте украинцы постоянно врёте Вот вы
you are lying and lying Like you As a lawyer You just
врёте и врёте вы Как вы Как юрист Вы
read the name of the court What kind of
прочитали название суда только что какой
court was Yours is an administrative District
был суд У вас административный Окружной
not a constitutional truth And what
не конституционный правда А у вас что
can you do right away in a constitutional way?
можно сразу в конституционно это раз
you confuse the
суда Верховный суд Нет ты путаешь
Supreme Court with the
Верховный суд с
constitution, even your sub-state
конституци даже ваше недо государстве
is the afterbirth, sir, no constitutional court
это послед сри нет конституционный суд
You can tell me what you
Вы можете рассказывать мне какие вы
want to say everything merged look
хотите сказать всё слился смотри
pressed searched searched in short I love these
нажимал искал искал короче Обожаю эти
moments when
моменты вот когда каких-то знаете росн
you know some Rosn fried And this is the guy who said that he is a lawyer just divine Khmelnitsky University of Management this is right like you in your suite the prophet the dude read it understood In short, something else is there, this is some kind of District Court Yes, he understood that this is not constitutional, he understands if he Lawyer that this is not an instance Yes, that there is a first court there, he understands that these are just courts, so if anyone is interested, what was it there in the Kyiv District Court, it was Yanukovych who filed it like or  I wanted to
это Янукович подавал вроде или хотел
submit that the title was removed from him,
подать то что с него сняли звание так
because the President of
потому что за президентом
Ukraine retains the title for life.
Украины сохраняется пожизненно звание
So, and accordingly, what kind of
Так ну и соответственно Какие пильги
benefits and all sorts of bonuses from the state,
льготы Да всякие бонусы от государства
then, in my opinion, in the month or in what year the
вот потом по-моему в м или в каком году
Supreme Council removed the
Верховный Совет снял с него
title of President from him, so he submitted  yes, so
звание президента вот он подавал это да
that the pilgi would be left for him, like, there was
чтоб пильги ему типа оставили вот в
no appeal from Yanukovych to the Constitutional Court.
Конституционный суд никакого обращения
I just adore
Януковича не было Я просто обожаю вот
moments like this when you know,
такие моменты когда знаете происходит
such heavenly pleasure happens, this guy,
такое Райское Наслаждение это чувак
first a daring military coup, everything and
сначала дерзкий военный переворот всё а
then oops  this is how you have to catch them And like
потом оп вот так их надо ловить И вот
this you should dunk for every word Why Because
так макать за каждое слово Почему Потому
they are goth you have an armed
что они гот у вас пошёл вооружённый
first generation Yes on what basis is it
первый род Да на основании чего это
military first military and oh not military
военно сначала военный а ой не воен
armed okay Everything is given here and where is the
вооруж окей Всё тут и дан где
armed coup And you removed
вооружённый переворот А вы сместили
Yanukovych Yes there  sme they were removed from
Януковича Да там как сме отстранили от
power stop how they were removed where now there
власти стоп как отстранили где сейчас
is a resolution there he reads he
есть постановление есть он читает он
reads he as a lawyer understands that there is no
читает он как юрист понимает что нету
word there removed and that the Supreme
там слова отстранили да что Верховный
Council simply recorded the fact that  he
Совет просто зафиксировал факт что он
himself eliminated yes, that is, if
само устранил да то есть если бы
Yanukovych returned Yes, the
Янукович вернулся Да
Supreme Council said that he himself
вот Верховный Совет о том что он само
eliminated, she didn’t, let’s say, removed
устранил она не ээ скажем сняла там с
some powers from Yanukovych Yes
Януковича какие-то полномочия Да
Yanukovych returns, he says I didn’t
Янукович возвращается говорит я не само
eliminate himself and I am Well, he continues his
устранил и я есть Ну и продолжает свою
activities in what  problem, but Yanukovych
деятельность в чём проблема но Янукович
didn’t return Yes,
не вернулся Да
uh, which confirms Yes, the resolution of the
эээ что подтверждает Да постановление
Supreme
Верховного
Council, the dude starts jumping there.
Совета чувак начинает прыгать там А
Why, in short, there’s an office there, it’s all lyrics
почему Короче там офис это всё лирика
in general, lyrics, who can even get a shufrich
вообще лирика кому там шуфрич может даже
in the nose  somewhere they gave yes there is a legal
в нос где-то дали да есть юридический
fact legal documents The guy
факт юридический документы Вот чувак
knows perfectly well that the constitutional court
прекрасно знает что конституционный суд
can only determine the
только может определять
constitutionality or non-
конституционность или не
constitutionality of that
конституционность того
normative legal act Yes, it’s a pity He
нормативно-правового акта Да жалко Он
ran away couldn’t stand it, I would have fried him
убежал не выдержал я бы его ещё пожарили
in the constitutional court because he
по конституционному суду потому что он
really wanted to say that  We, uh,
очень хотел сказать что у нас ээ
illegally changed something there, there is a
незаконно там что-то меняли есть
wonderful video on my channel
прекрасный ролик на моём канале
called the Trans-Ural Patriot. Eh, where are
называется там зауральский Патриот Э где
we there? We are roasting another blogger of theirs
мы там Жарим ещё одного ихнего блогера
on these constitutional courts on the Maidan
по этим конституционным судам по майдану
on  For Yanukovych, it’s just a heavenly
по Януковичу просто там Райское
pleasure, as he
наслаждение как он
sits with a sour face and reads,
с кислым фейсом сидит от читает
so
поэтому
look at the sad one, you know when
рассматривать грустного знаете когда его
we knocked him down with arrogance. This is a heavenly
мы сбили спеси Вот это Райское
pleasure, subscribe to the channel. Yes,
наслаждение подпишитесь на канал Да
like and like your
ставьте лайки тримайте своими
views of the komen for this purpose. So the videos
перегляд комен для того щоб Так видос
took off and we were taken off by the youth and
взлетали и ми отримували насолоду и
more people  Bachilo that the truth is on the
бильше бильше людей Бачило что правда на
side of Ukraine Glory to Ukraine caption on
сторони украини Слава Украине пидпись на
th Instagram I don’t know for  why is this for
й Instagram Я не знаю для чого це то для
what is there to marvel at otsey face Ale
чого тоб там дивитись на оцей фейс Але
for you tse odi two or three clicks Ale you
для тебе це оди два або три клика Але ты
trime me and I will be in me there Kupa
тримае мене и я буду к в мене там Купа
fouls and in me will be cool nybe robiti
фолов и в мене буде класный найб робити
but cool video message on th Instagram pok
но крут видео пись на й Instagram пок
Andriy
Андрий
otak  Let's get going
отак Давай тека
with
с